

John Restrepo

Full Stack .Net and SQL Developer

PROFILE



Self-taught and creative software developer with over 11 years of experience in producing robust code for high-volume companies mostly in Web Environments for many different industries using Microsoft Technologies. Eager to learn and grow professionally supporting and improving dev teams. In previous roles, increased code-efficiency and quality. boosted customer retention by 30% among others.

Under Canada Colombia FTA. Colombian citizens do not need a positive LMIA in order to work in Canada.

EXPERIENCE



2019 - Present Growth Acceleration Partners

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

Software development and Technology company with more than 300+ employees in multiple locations around the world.

- Lead the maintenance and new feature development of core applications for Health-care companies in The US and Canada.
- Give assistance to the application's main support team.

2014 - 2019 Sico S.A.S TECHNICAL LEAD

Software development startup which provides cloud solutions for real state companies in Colombia having 65% of market coverage. • Led the entire Product Development Lifecycle from building Business cases to production implementation.

- Executed & monitored the development, testing, and deployment of various features.
- Developed features for the main company's CRM Application.

2008 - 2014 Safyr S.A.S

PRODUCT LEADER

One of the most important software development companies in Colombia for the Financial Sector, provides web solutions with almost 70% Colombian market coverage using Microsoft Web Technologies.

- Developed & Deployed features in the company's integrator software.
- Build user stories and gathered the requirements analyzing user behavior to obtain preferences & finalize features.

EDUCATION



2009 - 2012

Remington University

GPA SYSTEMS ENGINEER

Degree in computer science with strong management knowledge of Software Development cycles.

2011 - 2012 Microsoft Certifications

MSSQL SERVER

Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist on Microsoft SQL Server 2008.

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate on Microsoft SQL Server 2012.

2005 - 2008 Remington University

SYSTEMS TECHNOLOGIST

Degree in computer science with general technical and focus knowledge on Software Development.

SKILLS



Developer Skills

C# .Net Developer

MSSQL Server Dev

Angular 4+ Developer

HTML 5 / CSS3 / Javascript



Language Skills

Spanish

English

